# TERESA A **BADER**

6717 South 91 Street, Omaha, NE 68127 | H: 402.331.7950 | C: 402-689-6384 | tabader@cox.net

#### Summary

Highly qualified registered nurse with a wide range of experience from critical care to perioperative nursing. Provides compassionate and patient focused care.

Experience outside the bedside in the roles of Clinical Consultant and Clinical Application Analyst. These positions focused on assisting clients during the implementation phases of installing electronic medical records. Demonstrated ability to easily adapt to new environments and situations.

#### **Skills**

- · Respected team player
- Supportive
- Responsible

- Positive
- Active listener
- Dependable

#### **Experience**

Infusion/Triage RN 02/2017 to 06/2017

#### Midwest Gastrointestinal Associates, PC

Omaha, NE

- Prepared and administered IV medications to patients with chron's disease and ulcerative colitis.
- Communication liaison between patient and physician.

Pre-op/PACU Staff Nurse 10/2016 to 01/2017

Nebraska Medicine

Omaha, NE

Provided direct patient care to surgical patients from Pre-op to PACU.

Staff Nurse 02/2016 to 09/2016

## **Lakeside Endoscopy Center**

Omaha, NE

- Provided direct patient care to patients undergoing GI procedures in an ambulatory surgery center.
- · Assisted physicians during procedures.

Triage Nurse 10/2015 to 12/2015

## **Think Whole Person Healthcare**

Omaha, NE

- Communication liaison between patient and physician.
- Scheduled patients for appointments, tests, and procedures.

#### Clinical Application Analyst

05/2014 to 10/2015

CHI Health

Omaha, NE

- Epic Certified, Clinical Documentation 2014.
- Assisted clients during the implementation phases of installing EPIC, an electronic medical record.

PACU RN 10/2011 to 04/2014

## **CHI Alegent Health Bergan Mercy Hospital**

Omaha, NE

Provided direct patient care to surgical patients from Pre-op to PACU.

Procedure Center RN 06/2006 to 10/2011

#### **CHI Alegent Health Lakeside Hospital**

Omaha, NE

- Provided direct patient care to surgical patients from Pre-op to PACU.
- Member of Unit Based Council.
- Charge nurse responsibilities.

#### Clinical Consultant

11/2004 to 06/2006

AmericanHealth Net Omaha, NE

- Provided client education and support on Clarus, an electronic medical record, on order entry and clinical documentation.
- Provided on-site support during go live.

RN 09/2002 to 11/2004

Intellestaf Healthcare Omaha, NE

• Provided direct patient care to critically ill adults at various hospitals in Omaha and the surrounding area.

Staff RN 01/1985 to 06/2002 Methodist Hospital Omaha, NE

• Provided direct patient care to critically ill adults with focus on open heart patients, ventilator dependent patients, IABP, and patients receiving multiple IV drips.

• Charge nurse responsibilities.

## **Education and Training**

RN Diploma

Methodist School of Nursing

Omaha, NE

**BLS Certified** 

**ACLS Certified**